[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Допомагати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "手伝ます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'допомога' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "手伝"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зачиняти' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "閉めます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Вимикати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "消します"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відчиняти' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "開けます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Спішити' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "急ぎます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Очікувати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "待ちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зупинятись' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "止まります"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Брати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "取ります"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Повертати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "曲がります"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Тримати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "持ちます"
    }
]
